har let me understand from you as far as
the earnings impact is concerned ICI
Lombard uh what's the uh you know what's
the brokerage uh coming in as far as
icis lombar is concerned well right uh
let me quickly take you through the
numbers first uh you know gross written
premiums at 5,600 CR that's up 177% for
ICI Lombard in Q3 we saw income from
Investments moreid 9% growth on a year
on-ear basis total expenses went up 14%
And expense ratios continued to be quite
elevated 30% plus uh with regard to
expense of management ratios but when
we're also looking at uh Pat therefore
Pat has com in at 11% higher when I'm
looking at it on a year-on-year basis
we're seeing combined ratio of around
104 a half uh which is obviously
continues to be slightly poor but
definitely improving Trends being seen
there in terms of what brokerages are
suggesting Philip Capital maintains a
buy uh gives it a Target price of, 1550
it says that the combined ratio remains
elevated
on the back of higher Opex the pat
growth is largely modest and they're
expecting operating performance of uh
the company to start improving going
forward they're they're positive on the
long-term prospects with regard to
growth in the non-life space as well in
terms of what Jeff is saying they
continue with a buy rating and a Target
price of 1620 they believe that earnings
were slightly below estimates and uh the
underwriting profits and investment
income is what is hurting profitability
uh what they're also suggesting is
spending uh is quite elevated with
regard to Marketing sales and the ramp
up in agency but that they also see as a
positive lastly mcquary believes that
it's an underperform they've given it a
Target price of $9.95 they believe that
Q3 has disappointed growth is largely
driven by health and especially by
retail Health motor remains a pain is
what they believe as a negative and they
believe valuations in the current
context are
expensive okay hsh that's all about ICI
Lombard but do stay on with and you know
as the shareholding pattern of HDFC and
HDFC bank is released analysts tell e
now that you know the merg entity is
likely to see as much as A6 Mill billion
dollar inflow harush what is the update
on this what are you understanding here
well yes absolutely right Vinnie you
know what analysts on the street are
penciling in is a$ 3 to6 billion inflow
into HDFC bank and that's large right uh
you know and the context to that is that
the shareholding pattern of HDFC uh
seems to suggest and the group
shareholding pattern seems to suggest
that there is a Headroom of 17 and a qu%
uh approximately which is well above the
15% limit uh this was mind you at 16.8%
just a quarter ago so clearly that
Headroom has now improved and that will
see some amount of foreign investment
coming through to the tune of at least
$3 billion so clearly at the moment the
overhang seems to be with regard to the
selling seems to be behind at least at
the moment the way we see it uh and with
fiis having a larger participation
that's further positive and further
upside which one can see here uh it's a
possibility with regard to the data as
well we did speak about valuations
yesterday uh with uh you know Anisha
there on the same show and we can see
that with regard to valuations there is
still some amount of catch up which HDFC
bank has and can potentially play going
forward as well so couple of positives
playing out quite well the stock is
buzzing today
absolutely it's very close to the
highest point of the trading session
thank you so much har for joining us and
talking to us about how uh the merged
entity could see inflows of anywhere
between three to6 billion dollar and
that's the heavy amount which is taking
the stocks higher as well but Delta